{"data":[{"question":"She _____ (see) your brother last week.","a":"seed","b":"seen","c":"saw","answer":"3","explain":"- See -> saw (see\/saw\/seen)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"You _____ (eat) too much last night.","a":"eat","b":"eated","c":"ate","answer":"3","explain":"- eat -> ate.(eat\/ate\/eaten)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"He _____ (look) at the picture last month.","a":"looked","b":"looken","c":"looke","answer":"1","explain":"- look -> looked (regular verb)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"The police _____ (catch) the thief last night.","a":"catched","b":"caught","c":"caughted","answer":"2","explain":"- catch -> caught (catch\/caught\/caught)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"Keiko _____ (not teach) Japanese.","a":"didn't teach","b":"didn't taught","c":"didn't teached","answer":"1","explain":"- Negative: did not\/didn't + infinitive.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"She _____(lose) her way?","a":"Did she lost","b":"Did she lose","c":"Did she losen","answer":"2","explain":"- Interrogative: did + subject + infinitive?","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"She _____ (find) her watch.","a":"did not find","b":"didn't found","c":"didn't finded","answer":"1","explain":"- Negative: did not\/didn't + infinitive.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"He _____ (sleep) badly last night.","a":"slepted","b":"slept","c":"sleeped","answer":"2","explain":"- sleep -> slept (sleep\/slept\/slept)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"Jack _____(keep) the money.","a":"didn't kept","b":"didn't keep","c":"didn't keeped","answer":"2","explain":"- Negative: did not\/didn't + infinitive.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"},{"question":"Tom _____(hurt) his foot?","a":"Did Tom hurt","b":"Did Tom hurted","c":"Did Tom hurtten","answer":"1","explain":"- The question form: Did + S + V...?","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"6"}]}